https://www.cat-health-guide.org/privacy-policy.html

We
recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of
personal information we receive and collect when you use The Cat Health Guide, as
well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will
help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
The
Cat Health Guide strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness
and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting
our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our website. These companies may use information (not including your
name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to
this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods
and services of interest to you. If you would like more information
about this practice and to know your choices about not having this
information used by these companies, click here.
Google and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on The Dog Health Guide site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to
visitors based on their visit to The Dog Health guide and other sites on the
Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the site Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Personal
Information
The
Cat Health Guide collects personally identifiable information from the visitors
to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary
basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and
telephone number.
This
information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a
contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some
other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed,
used to improve the content of our website, notify
our
visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once
information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make
material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we
will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from
any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or
provided to third parties.
Use
of Cookies and Web Beacons
We
may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are
identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web
browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a
cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For
example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's
services, a cookie enables (website/company name) to recall your specific information
on subsequent visits.
You
have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser;
however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully
experience the interactive features of the site.
A
web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a
single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs
and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor
traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how
visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.
We
may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the
course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've
seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is
provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally
identify you with that information on our web site.
Browsers
can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being
sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of
these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.
Children's
Online Privacy Protection Act
This
website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of
13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from
anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal
Information
In
some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally
identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual
users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements
around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a
whole.  The information collected is used
solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for
commercial purposes.
Release
of Information
If
The Cat Health Guide is sold, the information we have obtained from you through
your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a
part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue.
In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in
control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the
purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How
You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to download and review that information, click on this link.You can also request to edit or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on this link
Updates
and Effective Date
The
Cat Health Guide reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is
a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that
our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy.
We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what
information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing
to Terms
If
you do not agree to The Cat Health Guide’s Privacy Policy as posted here on
this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your
use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
About Us
Blog
Reader Questions
Privacy Policy
The Cat Health Guide is not intended to replace the advice of a Veterinarian or other Health Professional.
This site accepts advertising and other forms of compensation for products mentioned.
Such compensation does not influence the information or recommendations made.
We always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences.
All rights reserved. © 2020 Cat Health Guide.
